so here are the final results uh for
operation get strong and sexy six weeks
of
training um this is Aaron's first squat
blew that up I think that was
like 15 or something like that here's
Samy's first squat that was like 185
blew that up like it's nothing here's
Aaron's second squat I think this was
like
135 or something I can't can't remember
exactly I'm not good with these
kilograms yet uh paused real good went
deep blew that up like it's
nothing here's Sammy this is 198 this is
crazy here I've never seen this happen
so she goes down but she didn't wait for
the command so she comes up but then he
lets her go again and gives her the
command and then she gets it you can see
it was tough cuz she just did that of
the rep so she ended up with one a 198
Squad I think that tired her out though
here's Aon final Squad this is a PR you
can see she went below parallel looked
pretty easy that was 149 lbs that's the
most she's done and then here's Samy's
third squat this is like this is 210
she's done this in training but she just
didn't get it she goes really deep for
her that was deeper than normal I think
she was tired out from the last uh from
uh from her second
squat okay here is bench press um we
started out light with like I don't know
like 80 pounds or
something that was easy for Aaron here's
Sammy uh I think it was like 85 for her
uh blew that
up Aaron's next
bench uh tougher uh
than they had an both of them have an
had an off day with benching um in there
Samy's bench I think that was like
around 100 lb and then both of their
third I don't know what happened there
but Aon squeaked out that third bench
but got called on it because it wasn't
fluid it was choppy and then here's
Samy's third uh bench uh she didn't get
it she's done this in
competition but
uh just didn't quite get it um now
here's Samy's first deadlift we didn't
get Aaron's deadlifting I don't know why
what happened but sami's first deadlift
was easy it was like uh
two I don't know 27 two 265 or something
like that this this is like
275 here's Aaron we got one from our
iPhone I don't know what happened with
our video but this is 210 I think or
maybe it's lighter but she ended up
getting 210 which is a PR for her and
then here's Samy's last deadlift which
was 292 and this looked easy looks like
she could have done
300 um so she ended up with a 293 here's
just some pictures Aaron
squat
um Samy
squat um yep it was a really cool event
this is Aaron's
squat uh Sammy
squat next I think are some bench press
picks yep Aon bench press she had to put
her feet on the box so did Sammy because
Sammy was was used to benching on her
toes that was my bad I didn't teach her
that
rule um yep more bench
picks uh there's Samy's failed third
attempt she could have gotten the elbows
underneath her a little
more um and then here I think are some
deadlift picks Sammy pulling the weight
off the
floor locking out the
weight uh there's errands I believe that
was her second
attempt maybe that that was her second
attempt yeah and then this is yeah
there's
Sammy and then here's Aaron's this is
Aaron's 210 attempt you can see she set
up real good boom locked it out very
powerful she had a great day deadlifting
and this is sami's last attempt with the
deadlift locked it out
good um so very very happy with the
girls they kick butt there they are
after the show posing together one with
flash one without they like the picture
without Flash more and then here's the
three of us again without Flash and with
flash so and then here's one last one of
them flexing so so proud of you girls
great job Aaron and Sammy